TraceWarden SIFT proves seventeen DFIR claims in a recorded
run. The command writes receipts before findings reach the
The demo starts in the repo root. One command runs the
packaged case-alpha evidence and writes a fresh output folder.
The agent seals the evidence root, calls read-only parsers,
evaluates seventeen claims, and writes the reports. This is
CLAIM zero zero four fails. The timeline shows a signed
updater path, and no second source supports malicious
TraceWarden reroutes into PowerShell and network evidence.
CLAIM zero zero nine survives because two parsers point to the
The receipt is inspectable. It lists file, line, parser, hash,
and the tool calls behind the finding.
The accuracy report compares the run to ground truth. It
records sixteen confirmed claims, one revoked claim, zero
The tests cover path escape, report writing, schema safety,
and weak claim revocation. The demo does not rely on a hidden
The safety boundary stays below any planner: sealed evidence,
typed read-only tools, verifier-owned claim state, and
The repo includes the case, reports, deck, video source, and
tests. Run it, inspect CLAIM zero zero four, then add the next